You won't understand the reasons but I have to leave you here. Is it a game? When will
you come back for me? I'm not, David. You'll have to be here by yourself. Oh, with Tandy.
No. No, no, no, no. No, no. No, Mommy. Please, no. Please, no. I would destroy you, David.
You wouldn't know. I have to go. I have to go. Stop it. No, Mommy. I have to go. Mommy.
Mommy, if Pinocchio became a real boy and I become a real boy, can I come home?
It's just a story. This story tells what happens. Stories are not real. It's not that Mommy is real.
Now listen. Look. Look. Take this. All right. Take this. Don't let anyone see how much it is.
All right. Now look. Don't go that way. All right. Look. Look at me. Look. Don't go that way.
All right. Go anywhere, but that way or I'll catch you. Don't ever let them catch you.
Listen. Stay away from flesh fares. Away from there are lots of people. Stay away from all people.
Don't let them leave you. Let go.
I'm sorry. I didn't tell you about the world.